天啊  你打扫过了
Oh, my God, you cleaned!
瞧这地板  你还擦了窗户
Look at these floors! You did the windows!
我跟你提了好几个月  你真的打扫了
I have been begging you for months! And you did, you cleaned.
看来唠叨还是有用的
And nagging works!
不  事实上这不是我干的
No, I didn't actually do this.
不是吧  我又梦游打扫了吗
Oh, no. Was I cleaning in my sleep again?
不  也不是你
No, it wasn't you.
-那么是谁  -我请了一个女佣  耶
- Well, then, who? - I got a maid. Yay!
我希望你所说的"女佣"是指"情妇"
I hope by "maid" you mean "mistress"
因为如果有其他女人在打扫咱家房子的话
because if some other woman was cleaning...
亲爱的  我知道你不喜欢让出控制权
Now, honey, I know you don't like to relinquish control.
"让出"就是"失去"的委婉说法吧
"Relinquish" is just a fancy word for "lose."
她人真的很棒
She's really nice, okay?
她还说她喜欢你摆放海绵的方式
And she mentioned that she adored the way you arranged the sponges.
她真的那么说了吗
Did she really say that?
对  我记得很清楚  因为我以为她在开玩笑
Yes, I distinctly remember because I thought it was a joke.
给她一个机会  好吗
Now, just give her a chance, okay?
好吧  我办得到
Fine, I can do it.
怎么了
What's the matter?
通常我一焦虑就会打扫
Usually when I'm this anxious, I clean.
是谁的手机在响  吵死了
Whose cell phone is that? It's just so annoying.
走到哪里都会发生这种事
Everywhere you go.
我想声音是从你的包包里传出来的
I think it's coming from your bag.
从来没有人会打电话给我
I never get calls!
喂
Hello?
嗨  我是万圣节派对上的艾力克
Hi, it's Eric, from the Halloween party.
厄休拉的未婚夫
Ursula's fiance.
天啊  艾力克  嗨
Oh, my God, Eric, hi!
等一下  你怎么知道我的电话号码
Wait, how'd you get this number?
我有个警察朋友  他帮我查到的
I have a friend who's a cop, and he got it for me.
这严重侵犯了我的权利  但却让人又惊又喜
Wow. What an incredible violation and wonderful surprise!
我想告诉你
Listen, I just... I thought you should know
我跟厄休拉分手了
I broke up with Ursula.
是吗  他办到了
Oh, you did? He did it, he did it!
-他做了什么  -我在讲电话
- What did he do? - I'm talking!
总之我很好奇
Anyway, I was wondering
你平时吃不吃午餐
if you were the sort of person who eats lunch?
你是在约我吗
Are you asking me out?
因为那样会很奇怪
Because it'd be kind of weird
你刚刚才跟我姐姐分手
since you just broke up with my sister.
好吧  抱歉
Yeah, okay. I'm sorry.
-再见  -不  等一下
- Bye. - No, no. Wait!
我那么说是希望你觉得我是个好人
I was just saying that so you'd think I was a good person.
努力争取我吧
Fight for me.
我不会轻易接受你的拒绝
I won't take "no" for an answer.
虽然表现不太好  但我们可以边吃午餐边练习
Not great, but we can work on it at lunch.
我可以在两小时内赶到你家
I can be at your apartment in two hours.
太棒了  你怎么知道我住在哪里
Great. How do you know where I live?
我也有朋友
I've got friends too.
-好吧  再见  -再见
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
天啊  我要跟艾力克约会了
Oh, my God, I'm going out with Eric!
今天比我想像中
This day is really gonna be so much better
还要美好
than I thought it was gonna be.
罗斯  我没办法跟你吃午餐了
Oh, Ross, I can't make lunch.
很明显我午餐时间有空
So apparently I'm available for lunch.
不行  我很忙  我在找房子
I can't. I'm busy. I'm apartment hunting.
你要搬家
You're moving?
孩子生下来后我不可能跟乔伊一起住
I can't live with Joey once the baby comes.
我不希望我的孩子会说的第一句话是
I don't want my child's first words to be,
"你好吗"
"How you doing?"
乔伊知道你要搬家吗
So does Joey know you're moving?
我还没有跟他谈  但我知道他会觉得如释重负
I haven't discussed it with him, but I know he'll be relieved.
上星期他带了一个女孩回家
Last week, he brought this girl over,
我跟她谈晨吐的问题
and I talked to her about morning sickness.
还把我怀孕纪念册的照片拿给她看
Then I showed her pictures from my pregnancy book.
-内容不会很色情吧  -不太会
- That's not really porn? - Not so much.
既然你在找房子
You know what? If you're looking for a place,
今早我在电梯里听说
I just heard in the elevator this morning
我住的公寓里有个女住户过世了
that a woman in my building died.
天啊  她年纪很老了吗
Oh, my God. Was she old?
她的公寓景观好吗
Does she have a view?
我不知道  但那样一定会很棒
I don't know, but how great would that be?
你搬到我的公寓里来
You living in my building?
我可以照顾宝宝  想过去就过去...
I could take care of the baby, I could come over whenever I want...
当然得先得到你的允许
...with your permission.
那就太好了  我们能去看看吗
That really would be great. Well, can we see it?
或许我们不该那么做
Maybe we shouldn't.
毕竟她今天早上才过世
I mean, if she just died this morning out of respect.
对  你说得对
Yeah. No. No, you're right.
-我们去吧  -好啊
- Shall we? - Yeah.
有什么事吗
Yes?
嗨  我是罗斯·盖勒  住在这栋公寓里
Hi. I'm Ross Geller. I live in the building.
我是瑞秋  我很喜欢这栋公寓
And I'm Rachel, an admirer of the building.
听说佛哈芬太太过世了
I heard about Mrs. Verhoeven passing away,
我真的很遗憾
and I am so sorry for your loss.
-她没有过世  -什么
- She didn't pass away. - What?
我妈妈还活着
My mother's still alive.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God!
她今天早上差点就过世了
It looked like we were gonna lose her this morning,
但她是个意志力很强的老太婆
but she's a tough old bird.
你跟她很熟吗
Are you close with her?
当然  我们常常
Of course. She and I would talk all the time...
在洗衣间聊天
...in the laundry room.
你会说荷兰语吗
You speak Dutch?
很荣幸见到我母亲的朋友[荷兰语]
I'm very honored to meet a friend of my mother.
我会说  但说起来只会让我伤心
You know, I would, but it's just too painful.
她真的没死
So she's really not dead.
对  她还在坚持
No. She's hanging in there.
你能告诉我她是在一房还是两房里坚持吗
Could you tell me, is she hanging in in a one-bedroom or a two?
宾太太  这个清洁剂太棒了
Mrs. Bing, this tile cleaner is incredible.
你在哪里买的
Where did you get it?
那是我自制的
Oh, well... I make it myself.
两份的氨水加一份的柠檬汁
It's two parts ammonia and one part lemon juice.
秘方是...
The secret ingredient is...
你知道吗  我们才刚刚认识
You know what? We just met.
好吧  我去洗衣间拿衣服
Okay. I'm gonna go get the clothes from the laundry room now.
我回来后会打扫冰箱后面
When I come back, I'll clean behind the refrigerator.
我爱她
I love her.
我马上回来
I'll be back in a minute.
好吧
Okay.
看吧  我告诉过你
See? I told you.
她偷了我的牛仔裤
She stole my jeans!
什么
What?
我找了一个星期  她正穿在身上
I've been looking for them all week, and she is wearing them.
所以她偷了你的裤子
So she stole your pants
然后当着你的面穿在身上
and then came back and wore them in front of you?
你不明白吗  这是完美犯罪
Don't you see? It's the perfect crime!
她一定计划了好几年
She must have been planning this for years!
我会证明给你看
I'll prove it to you, okay.
几周前  我穿着那条牛仔裤
About a week ago I was wearing those jeans
我把钢笔掉在大腿上
and I dropped a pen in my lap,
在裆部留下了墨水印子
and it left an ink stain on the crotch.
她回来后
When she comes back,
我就让你看看那个墨水印子
I will find it and show you that stain!
亲爱的  卖那条牛仔裤的公司
Honey, isn't it possible the company that sold the jeans
难道只做了一条牛仔裤吗
made more than just the one pair?
说得有道理
I guess.
我们应该先找找看
So should't we give her the benefit of the doubt
再去看她的裆部吧
before we go snooping around her crotch?
好吧  幸好我没告诉她我的秘方
Fine. I'm just glad I didn't give her my secret ingredient.
我真的很好奇你的秘方是什么
Out of curiosity, what is your secret ingredient?
你想得美
Yeah.
请进  我很高兴你能过来
Come in. I'm so glad you're here.
对  我也是
Yeah. Me too.
但不像你那么震惊愤怒
Not in the shaky, angry way that you are, though.
抱歉  我刚刚见过厄休拉
Sorry. I just saw Ursula.
我得把订婚戒指拿回来
I had to get the engagement ring back.
看到她  让我想起了一切
Just seeing her brought it all back.
那些谎言  还有她是怎么利用我的
All the lies, the way she used me.
我只是...
I just...
光是看到她  我就觉得好生气...
I get so angry, just looking at her...
-我是说看到她的脸  -对
- Face. - Yeah. Yeah.
抱歉  我看到你的时候
I'm sorry. It's just, when I look at you...
我就像是看到了她
...I see her.
我看到她时
And when I see her,
就会觉得很生气
I get a little bit angry.
-这样太奇怪了  -等一下
- Maybe this is too weird. - Wait.
只有我看着你的时候才会觉得生气
There's only a problem when I look at you.
我知道了
I got it. I got it.
不  别把你的眼睛挖出来
No, don't tear out your eyes!
我只是要把隐形眼镜摘掉
I was just gonna take out my lenses.
好吧  试试看
Oh, yeah. Try that.
那样子好多了吗
So is that better?
才怪
Not really.
你看起来很模糊  还是很像厄休拉
You're blurry, but you still look like Ursula.
你是"模糊的厄休拉"
You're "Blursula."
好吧  等一下  也许
Okay, wait. Maybe...
我暂时不看你
If I just don't look at you for a while.
看吧  很有效果  我一点都不生气了
See? It works. I'm not angry at all anymore.
这次约会很成功
This is a great date!
听着  艾力克  转过来
Look, Eric, turn around.
我喜欢你  但不应该这么纠结
I like you, but it shouldn't be this hard.
这是我们第一次约会
This is our first date.
第一次约会应该是兴奋刺激  火花四射
First dates are supposed to be about excitement and electricity and...
"他刚刚摸了我的手  他是有意的吗 "
..."He just touched my hand, did he mean to touch my hand"
还有初吻
and you know first kisses...
第二次接吻
Second kisses.
谢谢你的咖啡  或者说
Thanks for the coffee, or:
谢谢你的咖啡  甘瑟[荷兰语]
bedankt voor de koffie, Gunter.
你会说荷兰话吗  真厉害[荷兰语]
You speak Dutch? That's cool.
你有亲戚在荷兰吗[荷兰语]
Do you have relatives there?
我们聊完了
Yeah, we're done.
混蛋
Ezel.
混蛋  混蛋
Ezel. Ezel.
罗斯
Hey, Ross. Listen.
你要去人工造浪池看新的立体巨幕电影吗
You wanna go see that new IMAX movie on tide pools?
-真的吗  -才没有
- Really? - No.
但我帮你  我跟钱德勒弄到了尼克队的门票
But I got Knicks tickets for you, me and Chandler.
太棒了
Sweet!
等你喝完咖啡  咱们就出发
All right, well finish your coffee, let's go.
我得先回家一趟
Okay. I have to stop by my place first.
你要录球赛吗  你每次都要录
To tape the game? You do this every time, Ross.
你是不会上电视的
You're not gonna be on TV!
不  我得去看看那间公寓是不是空出来了
No, I have to see if this apartment became available.
你要换公寓吗
You're switching apartments?
不是我  是瑞秋要搬家
It's not for me, it's for Rachel.
她已经有公寓了
Rachel has an apartment.
宝宝一出生  她就要搬家
Yeah, but when the baby comes, she's gonna wanna move.
-真的吗  -对
- She is? - Yeah.
你该不会希望她跟宝宝住在你那里吧
You didn't expect her to live there with the baby, did you?
我没仔细想过
I guess I didn't really think about it.
混蛋
Ezel.
甘瑟  你才是个混蛋
Hey, Gunther, you're an ezel.
你和混蛋性交了[荷兰语]
You have sex with donkeys.
该死
Damn it!
-你的牛仔裤很漂亮  -谢谢
- Nice jeans. - Oh, thanks.
-我喜欢你的上衣  -你别想得手
- I like your top. - Oh. You're not getting it.
-发生了什么事  -我睡着了
- What happened? - Oh. I fell asleep!
我想要午休一下
I was thinking about taking my lunch break.
你能擦一下橱柜上面吗
Will you do the top of the cabinets?
那会让你午餐时食欲大增
That'll work up your appetite for lunch.
好吧
All right.
你好啊
Hello.
发生了什么事
What's going on?
抱歉  我以前没请过女佣
I'm sorry. I've never had a maid before.
这样做不合适吗
Is this not okay?
球赛怎么样
How was the game?
还不错  我吃太多了
It was okay. I ate way too much.
我跟罗斯谈过  他说你在找新公寓
I was talking to Ross, and he said you were looking for a new place.
对  我希望能搬到对街去
Yeah. Hopefully across the street.
如果那些荷兰人愿意让出公寓
If certain Dutch people would just let go.
我希望你留下来
I was kind of hoping you'd stay.
乔伊  我得搬走  这里容不下一个宝宝
Joey, I have to go. There's no room for a baby here.
容不下  宝宝也就这么大吧
No room? It's a baby. It's, like, this big.
你可以把他放在这里
You could put it over here.
或是这里  很可爱吧
Or we could put it right here. It's cute, right?
或是这里  你根本就不会注意到他
Or put it over here. You wouldn't even notice it.
"宝宝在哪里 "  "他就在..."
"Where's the baby?" "Oh, it's right over..."
亲爱的  问题不仅在于要把他放在哪里
Honey, it's not just a matter of where you put it.
宝宝会让你的生活翻天覆地
A baby changes everything.
他们总是哭个不停
They cry all the time.
如果你带女孩回家
Imagine bringing home some girl
想跟她上床时  宝宝却哭个不停
and trying to score with a screaming baby around.
我可以接受这个挑战  算不上什么难事
I could use a challenge. It's getting pretty easy.
你要我留下来  真的很贴心
It's so sweet that you want me to stay,
但我不能那么对你
but I can't do that to you.
那样会毁了你的生活
It would disrupt your entire life.
只是...
It's just...
我很喜欢跟你一起住
I love living with you so much.
-我希望一切都不必改变  -我知道
- I wish things didn't have to change. - I know.
这件事全怪罗斯
You know, I blame Ross for this.
我也有点怪他
I do too, a little bit.
我会想念你的
I'm gonna miss you.
你是我遇过最辣的室友
You're the hottest roommate I ever had.
不行  我得走了  有人预约我去按摩
Oh, no, I have to go. I have a massage appointment.
别  留下来  我们继续吧
No, stay here. We'll keep doing this.
我可以付钱给你
I'll pay you.
不行  之前我因为这个惹上了大麻烦
No, I've gotten in trouble for that before.
-待会见  -没问题
- I'll see you later? - Absolutely.
我喜欢你的吻技
I love the way you kiss.
真的吗  那是我最逊的方面
Really? That's the thing I'm worst at!
你等着瞧吧
You'll see.
-我觉得布兰达需要加薪  -为什么
- Hey. I think Brenda needs a raise. - How come?
因为我把头放在她的双腿之间
Because I put my head between her legs.
-为了看她的裤子吗  -那是我的裤子
- To see her pants? - They're my pants!
你确定吗  你看到墨水印子了吗
Are you sure? Did you see the stain?
没有  我才刚刚就位  就眼前一片漆黑
No. I was getting into position, and then everything went dark.
她没有偷我们的东西  你能不能算了
She is not stealing from us, okay. Will you let this go?
好吧
Fine.
-她穿着我的胸罩  -天啊
- She's wearing my bra! - Oh, dear God!
我的粉红色小花胸罩  我认得那条肩带
My pink, flowered bra! I recognize the strap!
那你没意识到自己疯了吗
Yet you don't recognize that you're crazy?
我有个计划
Here's the plan.
我先离开  你去看布兰达的胸罩
I'm going to leave, and you're gonna look at Brenda's bra.
我也有个计划
Here's another plan.
不要
No.
本可以由我来做  但她以为我喜欢她
I would do it, but she thinks I'm attracted to her.
为什么
Why?
你不知道刚刚我的头插到哪里了吗
Did you not hear where my head was?
我们是一帮的  在这件事上应该同进退
Come on, come on. We're a team. We're in this together.
我担心陪审团也会那么认为
I fear a jury will see it the same way.
就算是为了我
Do this for me.
我常抓到你在瞄女人胸部
I catch you looking at womers breasts all the time.
你看到了吗
You see that?
这样难道你看不到吗
Do you see this?
好吧  我了解你的意思
All right, yes. Okay. I get your point.
但如果那不是你的胸罩
But if it's not your bra,
你能让她接着安心打扫吗
will you just let the woman clean the apartment?
没问题
Yes. Absolutely.
是不是我的你能分辨出来  因为在右罩杯上
You'll know it's mine because on the right cup,
蕾丝的部分  有明显的开线
the lacey part, there's a very noticeable rip.
你需要买新衣服了
You need new clothes.
-她还好吗  -情况看起来不妙
- Hi. How is she? - It's not looking good.
我带了一些花过来给她
Well, I brought her some bloemen.
你太体贴了  你要跟她送别吗
That's so sweet. Would you like to come in and say goodbye?
那对她来说一定意义重大
I'm sure it would mean a lot to her.
这我还真没想到
Oh, I don't know that it would.
-她几乎不记得任何人了  -那么好吧
- Well, her memory is pretty much gone. - All right, then.
欢迎你回来
Welcome back.
我们要继续吗
Shall we pick up from where we left off?
今天下午过后  我还没缓过劲来
I don't know. I'm still tired from this afternoon.
-为什么  -我们做爱了
- Why? - The sex.
-什么  -你跟我做爱了
- What sex? - Our sex.
我们没做爱啊
We didn't have sex.
如果我没跟你做爱
If I didn't have sex with you,
我一定是跟一个长得跟你很像...
I had sex with somebody that looked an awful lot like...
不会吧
Oh, no. Oh, no.
No, no, no.
-你跟厄休拉做爱了  -做了一点
- You had sex with Ursula? - A little bit.
她走进来  我以为她是你  我吻了她...
She walked in, I thought she was you and I kissed her and...
你没注意到衣服不一样吗
You didn't notice different clothes?
我看到你太兴奋了
I was just so excited to see you.
这真的是太奇怪了
You know what? This is too weird.
不会的  我不想失去你
No, it's not. I don't wanna lose you.
在做爱的时候
It's like I was saying to Ursula
我以为厄休拉是你  我对她说...
when I was making love to her and I thought she was you...
对  那太奇怪了
Yeah. It's too weird.
那就到此为止吧
So I guess this is it.
好
Yeah.
或许这是最好的办法
Maybe it's for the best.
-你的味道跟她一样  -对  你也是
- You smell just like her. - Yeah, so do you.
-你在做什么  -我在屈伸
- What are you doing? - I'm leaning.
我都在这里做屈伸运动
This is where I lean.
好吧
Okay.
-布兰达  有蜜蜂  -什么
- Brenda, a bee! - What?
它飞进你上衣里了
Yes! It's flown into your blouse,
你最好快解开扣子  免得被叮伤
and you better undo your buttons lest it sting you.
-我想我知道这是怎么一回事了  -是吗
- I think I know what's going on here. - You do?
你太太是女同志  我知道你一定很难受
Look, I know it must be hard that your wife is a lesbian...
但这是不对的  你结婚了
...but it's wrong. You're married.
-我完全了解  -太好了
- I totally understand. - Okay, good.
我能看看你的胸罩吗
Could I just see your bra?
-你怎么会有那条牛仔裤  -是你送我的
- Where'd you get those jeans? - You gave them to me.
-我才没有  -好吧  是我自己拿的
- No, I didn't! - All right, I took them.
我以为你不会介意
I figured it'd be okay
因为在裆部的地方有一大块墨水印子
because you've got a big ink stain on the crotch.
不要啊  你也拿走了我的胸罩吗
Oh, no! Did you take my bra too?
什么胸罩
What bra?
有小花的粉红色胸罩
The pink one with the flowers.
你是说你正穿的这件胸罩吗
You mean the one you're wearing?
我不干了
I quit!
可以理解
Sounds about right.
这是什么
What is this?
我只是做一下大致构想
This is just to give you an idea.
我们可以在这里装拉帘  给宝宝留有隐私
We can put screens here so that the baby has privacy...
在摇篮上面装个音乐铃
...and maybe a mobile over the crib...
这是宝宝监控器
...and here's a baby monitor
宝宝没出生前  我们可以把它当对讲机
which, till the baby comes, we can use as walkie-talkies.
你真的是太体贴了
You're so sweet!
天啊  你帮宝宝买了企鹅宝宝
Oh, my God! And you gave the baby Hugsy!
我只是要向你示范宝宝该躺在哪里
That's really just to show where the baby would go.
快把它交给我吧  免得你误会了
Why don't I hold on to him so there's no confusion.
乔伊  宝宝会哭的  那会非常地吵
Joey, the baby is gonna be crying. It's gonna be loud.
-我本身就很吵  -他会整晚不睡
- I'm loud. - It's gonna be up all night.
-我也会  -他会大便
- I'm up all night. - It's gonna poop.
难道我不是吗
Hello!
那你带回家的姑娘们怎么办
What about all the women you wanna bring home?
如果我把一个姑娘带回家
Look. If I'm bringing home a woman
她连和宝宝相处都做不到
who can't stand being around a baby...
那或许我根本不该跟那个姑娘在一起
...then maybe I don't wanna be with that woman.
或许我们该在酒吧的洗手间里做爱
Or maybe we'll do it in the bathroom of the club!
乔伊  你确定吗
Joey, are you sure?
对  听着  我知道有时候会很辛苦
Yeah. Look, I know sometimes it'll be hard, okay...
但同时也会非常幸福愉快
...but it'll also be really, really great.
拜托  瑞秋  我真的希望你留下来
Please, Rachel, I really want you to stay.
我也想留下来  谢谢你
I want me to stay too. Thank you.
乔伊  看看这个摇篮  好可爱
Joey, look at this crib. It's so cute.
我知道  我是在街上捡到的
I know. I found it on the street.
你是...  真的吗  看起来还不错
Are you...? Really? This is in such good condition.
是啊
Yeah.
被子下面是什么
Whoa! What's under the cover?
-我不知道  -它在动
- I don't know. - It's moving.
它长了尾巴  快把它搬出去
It's got a tail! Get it out of here!
好吧
Okay!
那位老太大过世了  我怎么会知道呢
Well, the old lady died. And how do I know?
因为她的遗愿是给她最后一吻
Because her dying wish was for one last kiss.
但我不在乎
But I don't care,
因为你拿到那间公寓了  太棒了
because you got the apartment. Yes!
是啊
Yeah.
我想要留在这里
I think I'm gonna stay here.
很棒吧
Isn't that great?
什么  你...但是...
What...? You... But... Bu...
两个混蛋
Ezels.